Hi everybody. So many of you wonder how
hijab is worn. I'm not going to unravel
mine obviously to show you. So I have my
little one here cuz hijab is not
mandatory on young children. So here's
what you're going to need. You're going
to need a scarf, usually rectangular, an
underscarf, which is this piece right
here, a scrunchie or something to hold
the hair, and a hijab magnet. Okay, so
I'm going to put her hair up in a bun,
kind of like a half bun type scenario,
just like this. And then this underscarf
is obviously an adult underscarf, but
I'm going to put it on her. We're gonna
slide it up like this. And all this does
is it is so cute. Holds the hair in
place. So, I'm going to take my hijab
magnets and I'm going to just pin it
just like that. And toss it over. And
there you go. There you have it. There's
your hijab. I love it. I want to keep
it. I want to hold it. A,
you're so cute.